IDO POSTELNIK

postelnik@gmail.com • (+972)54-808-0474 • Tel-Aviv, Israel

ABOUT ME

During my career as a Front End Developer and UX/UI Designer, I've been focusing on creating products with an emphasis on great user experience and with attention to the smallest details.

I'm responsible, thorough, organized, self-taught, hard-worker, and willing to learn from the best.

EXPERIENCE

SpotinstTel-Aviv, IsraelFront End Developer2018-Present

- Managing the front-end and product aspects in my scrum team.
- Developing features for the products' UI platform that presenting dashboards, charts and creation wizards.
- Leading and managing new features and projects.
- Building the backend-UI for the server side using nNode.js.

PlayerMaker Tel-Aviv, Israel

Front End Developer and UX/UI Designer

2016-2018

- Built the product's console from scratch. The console included tables, charts and special UI elements.
- Worked closely with the product team to prototype and define the product.
- Built wireframes, graphical designs and interactive moquaps.

<u>Israel Defence Force</u>

Israel

Squad commander - Artillery Forces

2008-2011

- Commanded on a squad of 10 soldiers.
 - Managed self-propelled gun (Tomat).
 - Chosen to represent the IDF in the Jewish Agency delegation to Winnipeg, Canada.

EDUCATION

Technion - Israel Institute of Technology

Haifa, Israel

Bachelor of Science, Information Systems Engineering

2012-2016

- Under the Industrial Engineering and Management faculty.
- Designed and developed a recommendation system web app based on AI algorithm.
- Led a consulting project that improved business performance and efficiency by 40%. This project is now used as a use-case in consulting classes.

SKILLS

Code

JavaScript, HTML5, CCS3, SCSS, Bootstrap4, AngularJS, Angular, React.Js, Vue.js, Flutter, Node.js, Koa, Express.js, MongoDB, MySQL, Wordpress, Git, AWS, GCP, Kubernetes.

UX and Design

Invision, Balsamiq, Figma, Sketch, Adobe Experience Design, Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects, Premiere.